<u>Iunina.anastasiya@gmail.com</u>

https://www.linkedin.com/in/anastasia-lunina/

https://github.com/AnastasiaLunina

Medium blog:https://medium.com/@lunina.anastasiya

Portfolio: https://anastasia-codes.netlify.app/

FULL STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Former QA Engineer now Full Stack Software Developer with 3 total years of experience in a tech field who appreciates quality, properly tested and refined software. The QA background allows me to see a product from a different angle. Able to trouble-shoot the issues effectively and apply the right fix in a quicker manner. Can perfectly work independently as well as in a team. Well organized with strong attention to detail with ability to prioritize and manage various tasks, critical thinker, who is always analyzing and assessing problems and implications, identifying patterns, making connections of underlying issues.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming: Python, OOP, Django, Docker, REST API, SQL, JavaScript, React, Typescript, HTML, CSS, AJAX, & JSON, Webpack

Databases: Oracle, MySQL, PostgreSQL, ORM

Version Control: Git/GitHub

Platforms: Windows, Mac. UNIX/LINUX

Testing Tools: Postman

Other: AutoCAD, SolidWorks, Adobe, Figma, Jira/Xray

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer, Self-employed Sept 2020 - Present

- Met with the prospective clients to gather specifications for new or existing websites
- Design, Implement and test the Web UI interface applications using HTML5, CSS, JavaScript
- · Prepared multiple designs and wireframes for clients' approval before proceeding with development
- Maintained and optimized digital properties for SEO
- Conducted testing of websites across all major browsers to ensure quality and consistency throughout
- Redesigned website to a clean modern minimalistic design with complete mobile responsiveness.
- Working with Source Control Management such as Git
- Used Django, ORM, PostgreSQL to develop user friendly applications

Software QA Engineer, Q-Softpro, Inc., Remote Jun 2020 - Present

- Tested Web-based applications developed by the company's clients
- Worked with Product Owner and Development Team to ensure all requirements were met
- Developed and executed test cases, using Xray /Jira to monitor test executions, and capture results
- Executed Smoke and Regression testing for every new build
- Performed API testing based on Swagger, created and automated collections using JavaScript and ran them using Postman
- Developed and executed SQL queries to validate frontend and backend data integrity (MySQL, PostgreSQL)
- Participated in a full Software Development Life Cycle, starting from planning til maintenance stage
- Worked in Agile/ Scrum environment, actively participated in Stand-Up meetings, Sprint Planning meetings, and Sprint

Retrospective meetings, provided input on the application functionality and testing process improvement recommendations

• Took an active role in project planning, including translating product requirements into deliverable pieces and sequencing them in a manner that brings value to the business

Drafting Manager, ESF Inc., New York, NY Sep 2016 - Mar 2020 • Followed specifications and calculations to create drawings for various projects

- Visited sites, making necessary measurements for future drawings
- · Communicated with architects and engineers, and incorporated knowledge gained into drawings
- Ensured final designs were compliant with building regulations
- Identified and communicating potential design problems to the project team
- Prepared both rough sketches and detailed work using CAD systems

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree in Economics, Southern Federal University, Rostov, Russia

Please see the Project section below:

ANASTASIA LUNINA

<u>Iunina.anastasiya@gmail.com</u>

https://www.linkedin.com/in/anastasia-lunina/

https://github.com/AnastasiaLunina

Medium blog: https://medium.com/@lunina.anastasiya

Portfolio: https://anastasia-codes.netlify.app/

FULL STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

👘 New York, NY 🌭 (631)406-3798

PROJECTS

Vkinder. Backend App coded in Python.

Chat-bot interacting with the database of social media network vk.com. Bot collects the user's info by getting the user's ID through API and based on that offers three images of people, who matches the user's interests, along with person's info, built as a dialogue with the user. Users can decline or add to match to favorites. All data is written to a database. Users can look at their favorites list or at black list at any time.

<u>Technologies used:</u> Python, Postgresql, Sqlalchemy, API, requests library <u>Link to the project: GitHub</u>

Backup to cloud. Backend App coded in Python.

Program which copies photos from vk.com to cloud storage on Yandex.disc. Program chooses largest image, renames image based on likes quantity, creates folder on Yandex disc and copies images to created folder. Technologies used: Python, API, requests library

Link to the project: GitHub

- JS_Track_Finance_App. Frontend App coded in JavaScript using classes and API.

JavaScript app. Users can register, login, logout, create personal app accounts. Users are able to track several bank accounts. Users can add or delete new transactions, see the list of all transactions for each bank account.

<u>Technologies used:</u> JavaScript <u>Link to the project: GitHub</u>

- JS_Food_App. Frontend App coded in JavaScript.

App for healthy food services. API, Slider, calculator, modal, countdown <u>Technologies used:</u> JavaScript <u>Link to the project: GitHub</u>